<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ZTDBP on ZTDBP Blog</title><link>https://ztdbp.xyz/ztdbp_blog/tags/ztdbp/</link><description>Recent content in ZTDBP on ZTDBP Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>&amp;copy 2022 ZTDBP</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:15:18 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ztdbp.xyz/ztdbp_blog/tags/ztdbp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ZeroData WhitePaper</title><link>https://ztdbp.xyz/ztdbp_blog/zerodata-whitepaper/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 16:15:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ztdbp.xyz/ztdbp_blog/zerodata-whitepaper/</guid><description>Zero Data White Paper Thank you for your attention to Zero Data. Zero Data helps organizations improve database security by providing a better and simpler way to protect your database security.
The information contained in this document is designed to provide customers and potential customers with the security status, practices and processes of Zero Data. Zero Data ensuring database security is a continuous improvement process, and we will continue to evaluate and support it.</description></item><item><title>ZTDBP Best Practices</title><link>https://ztdbp.xyz/ztdbp_blog/ztdbp-best-practices/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 14:19:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ztdbp.xyz/ztdbp_blog/ztdbp-best-practices/</guid><description>ZTDBP Practice This paper mainly records the rapid implementation and deployment of the main projects of ZTDBP, as well as the necessary configuration of each project, so as to realize the zero trust network security platform as soon as possible.
Get Start Our zero-trust platform initialization relies on the basic components of Mysql, ZACA and ZAManager. The following is the deployment method we have prepared for you for your reference. You can customize and modify it and use it better.</description></item><item><title>ZACA project introduction</title><link>https://ztdbp.xyz/ztdbp_blog/zaca-project-introduction/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 18:35:28 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ztdbp.xyz/ztdbp_blog/zaca-project-introduction/</guid><description>ZACA ZACA is a PKI developed based on cloudflare cfssl,Public key infrastructure (PKI) governs the issuance of digital certificates to protect sensitive data, provide unique digital identities for users, devices and applications and secure end-to-end communications.
Zaca includes the following components：
TLS service, as the CA center, is used for certificate issuance, revocation, signature and other operations. API services, as some API services for certificate management. OCSP service is a service that queries the online status of certificates and has been signed by OCSP.</description></item><item><title>ZeroAccess WhitePaper</title><link>https://ztdbp.xyz/ztdbp_blog/zeroaccess-whitepaper/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 22:55:18 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://ztdbp.xyz/ztdbp_blog/zeroaccess-whitepaper/</guid><description>Thank you for your interest in ZeroAccess ZeroAccess helps organizations improve information security by providing a better and simpler way to protect access to private network resources and applications.
The information contained in this document is intended to provide customers and potential customers with transparency and confidence about the security situation, practices and processes of ZeroAccess. Although this document represents the security of ZeroAccess when it was last updated, ensuring information security is a process of continuous improvement, and we will not stop the evaluation and support.</description></item></channel></rss>